("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
♫ In the not too distant future
♫ Way down in Deep 13
♫ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank
♫ Were hatchin' an evil scheme
♫ They hired a temp by the name of Mike
♫ Just a regular Joe they didn't like
♫ Their experiment needed a good test case
♫ So they conked him on the noggin
♫ And they shot him into space
- [Mike] Let me go!
♫ We'll send him cheesy movies
♫ The worst we can find
♫ He'll have to sit and watch them all
♫ And we'll monitor his mind
♫ Now keep in mind Mike can't control
♫ Where the movies begin or end
♫ He'll try to keep his sanity
♫ With the help of his robot friends
♫ Robot roll call
♫ Cambot (show yourself)
♫ Gypsy (I'm not ready)
♫ Tom Servo (hello there)
♫ Crow (that's one "o")
♫ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♫ And other science facts
♫ Just repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show,
♫ "I should really just relax
♫ "For Mystery Science Theater 3000" ♫
(doors slamming)
- Well, hi, everyone.
Mike Nelson here, along
with Crow and Servo
aboard the Satellite of Love.
I thought we'd start things
a little differently,
and why don't you join us
as, each in our own way,
we observe a moment of silence.
- God, this is great, eh?
This is so spiritual, I just
can't believe it (chuckles)
You know what this silent thing is like?
Well, I'll tell ya.
I feel like one of them
Trapper Monks or somethin'!
(chuckles) No kidding, really!
I feel so purified, my soul is as smooth
as a baby's behind (chuckles).
And I'm not just talkin'
insights here, no sir.
I'm talkin' vision!
I'm talkin' full-blown illumination!
I'm talkin' about revelations
shouted down from the mountain top.
I'm talkin' huge, deafening
thunder claps of truth.
We're beyond mere silence here, friends.
We're in a mega silence!
You've heard about the Big
Bang theory of silence?
This isn't "Mad Talk"!
Boom! (cackles) Boy, is it quiet!
Wowee, is this silence or what?
I feel enlightenment, it's satori,
it's like I'm sittin'
under the Bodhi tree!
Wow! Ha ha!
That was some round of silence, eh, gents?
- [Mike and Crow] Yeah.
- Well, hey, it doesn't have to end now.
Heck, I could be silent like this all day!
- Oh, you can't, 'cause Mike Johnson
and Todd Langus are calling.
- Who's that?
- Uh, I went to grade school with them.
- Well, how the hell
are we supposed to know
the people you went to grade school with--
(arguing indistinctly)
(doorbell ringing)
- Just a minute, Mike.
(door creaKing)
(heavenly music)
- [Both] Our Chinese food!
- Here, keep the dime.
You did a great job.
- OK, let's see here.
Hope they didn't forget
my tangerine chicken.
Nope, here it is.
And my chicken with broccoli.
My chicken with baby corn.
My chicken with peanuts.
My chicken in a distinctive sauce.
My chicken in sweet and
sour sauce with lemongrass.
- Where's my mock duck?
- "Where's my mock duck?"
(chuckles) I'm kidding.
Here, why don't you send
some of this stuff up
to the Satellite of Love, OK?
- OK.
- Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want this.
I'm going to eat my fortune cookie first.
(laughs) I'm so naughty.
(crunching)
Oh, oh.
"You have been summoned to
a place beyond this earth.
"A place beyond your understanding.
"A place filled with laughter and love,
"safety and happiness, for all eternity.
"A trusted friend will
accompany you to this
"other plane of existence,
"and your journey will begin.
"Watch for the signs, my friend.
"Godspeed and good luck."
What a crappy fortune.
Clay, open yours.
- Uh, you will die alone and afraid,
knowing not a single human
being ever loved you.
Lucky numbers 3, 18, 80...
It's weird, I keep getting the same one.
What about you, Nelson,
have you gotten your order?
- Uh, yeah, I believe so.
Crow, you got your lo mein, then?
- Well, actually it's the
Death of a Salesman Special,
and that came with the Willie lo mein.
(smacKing and slurping)
- Well, no matter.
I'm just gonna enjoy my hot and sour
seafood and giant clam soup.
Cracker in there.
(clack)
Ah! What the...
Ooh.
OK, come on, come on.
Ooh, ow! Ooh, ooh, ow, ow!
- (chuckles) You kids with
your weird Chinese foods.
Just gimme a good ol'
American hot dog any day.
(barKing)
What, no! Oh, no, no, no!
Stop it, no!
(ticklish laughter)
- OK, Frank, I've got the napkins
and the beverages, we can start eating.
Well, Mike, your movie this week
is a tasty fried dumpling called
"Samson Versus the Vampire Women,"
and it's served with a
tangy hot and sour sauce.
(boxes tumbling)
Frank, did you leave me any food?
- Well, there's plenty of soy sauce.
- Oh, thank you.
I don't want any soy sauce.
- Gimme that, you!
(barKing)
(snarling and growling)
(sirens sounding)
(gears grinding)
(chuckling and sighing)
- [Mike] Whoa, Capital Critters is on.
- [Crow] Why do they have the
blue mosque as they're symbol?
- [Servo] Granted he
is The Silver Maskman.
You didn't need to tell us that.
- [Mike] Samson the
Silver Maskman Tattaglia.
- [Crow] And Delta Burke as Delilah.
(ominous music)
- [Servo] AKA the Silver Maskman
Versus the Vampire Women.
- [Mike] A light-hearted romp about
the war between the sexes.
- [Crow] Samson Versus the Vampire Women:
A Major Supreme Court Case.
- [Servo] Y'know, suddenly I'm in the mood
for a Black Castle hamburger.
- [Mike] Uh-huh, and
directed by Joe Smith.
(snickering)
- [Crow] Remember there are vampire women,
so uh, get ready with the Cher jokes.
- [Servo] Isn't this the castle
from the bottom of a fish bowl?
- [Mike] What you call hell,
Ramos calls photography.
- [Servo] We gratefully
acknowledge the cooperation
of the Churubusco-Azteca Film Board.
- [Crow] With special
assistance by G. Gordon Liddy.
I dreamed I visited El
Manderly last night.
♫ Yes, the movie sucks, Fernando ♫
- [All] Fabian? Aaaaah!
- [Servo] The rest of this
neighborhood is just modest
ranch homes.
- [Mike] You know I went to school
with an Alfonso Corona Blake.
- [Servo] You did?
- [Mike] No wait, that was
Todd Langston, I'm sorry.
(scoffs)
(owl hooting)
- [Mike] Owls imitating a spider monkey.
- [Servo] Well, I think
this house is ready to show.
(thunder rolls)
- [Mike] Must be the maid's century off.
- [Servo] Oh, they keep
the vase nice and polished.
- [Crow] Yup, one of
Newt's orphanages here.
- [Mike] Um-hum.
- [Crow] Kee, kee.
- [Mike] I'll be back, Alfred.
- [Crow] Hey, it's Cob.
- [Servo] (laughing then scoffs)
It's like Ms Havisham's summer place.
- [Mike] Suzanne Pleshette.
- [Servo] Isn't it strange
how her eyes don't follow you,
no matter where you are in the room.
- [Crow] Established, 1761.
(fearful screaming)
- [Servo] Someone tapped over Seinfeld.
(door creaks open)
Surprise.
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
- [Crow] Fang? Are you out there?
Ha ha!
- [Mike] Oh, it's Ginger Rodgers. Whew.
- [Crow] Ah.
- [Servo] Lady. I guess we
caught you at a bad time lady.
- [Crow] Let the Cher jokes, begin.
- [Servo] Hey, it looks like Cher.
(laughter)
- [Mike] I don't tan.
- [Servo] Did I miss the alarm?
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Ah, the place hasn't changed.
- [Mike] Oh, I'm the first one up again,
so I'll make breakfast.
- [Servo] She's so thin.
I hate her.
- [Crow] This would be
a good place to come
if you were moving and needed boxes.
- [Mike] By Wammo.
- [Servo] Where did I put my pantyhose?
- [Crow] Eck, boy Angie
Dickinson has hit a rough spot.
- [Servo] She's dressed
like Jeremiah Johnson.
♫ Oh what a beautiful morning ♫
- [Crow] This place needs a plant.
- [Servo] I think this is back when
glam rock was really big.
- [Mike] Can they keep this pace up?
- [Crow] All right Marines,
grab your socks and drop your
socks.
- Thorina.
- [Servo] You over slept.
- Queen and mistress of the night.
Lady of darkness and mentor
of the vampire women.
You have rested 200 years now.
- [Mike] This is not a hotel, young lady.
- You slumbered for
centuries, just as you are.
Your master has not
summoned you until now.
The hour is here at last.
You are to make the prophecies
he laid out come true.
He reigns in the dark dominion.
He, your lordly husband calls.
Your sovereign.
- [Crow] Just one more century.
- All men are addicted to corruption,
and obligated to seek self destruction.
- [Servo] Hey!
Well, that's true actually.
- They have committed us all,
to awaken and call out the monsters
that reside on this earth.
(wolf howls)
- [Servo] Would you shut up.
Some people gotta work in the morning.
- [Crow] Le nails, ah.
- [Mike] I know this isn't right to say,
but this is an ugly sorority.
- [Servo] Chinese fire drill.
- [Crow] I don't mind
if their hair is long,
as long as it combed.
- [Mike] Mink.
With clapformate.
(laughter)
- [Crow] I call the bathroom first.
- [Servo] The eczema support
group meets in the basement.
- [Mike] Oh, maybe a
humidifier would help.
- Thorina.
Honor of the coven of the vampire women.
At last the moment has arrived
when we must select your successor.
So that you will be free
again, to return to the great
depths of the earth.
To occupy your throne at his side.
- [Crow] First the minutes
from the last meeting.
- To all mortal lives.
A Queen of the most radiant beauty.
- [Servo] Huh.
- Because you are destined
to scourge and seduce men.
- [Servo] Well, wake that lady up.
Come on.
- And you as well my sisters.
I call--
- [Servo] No tag backs.
- I, Tandra.
The one selected to order
and guide you as priestess of
vampires.
I must carry out my mission.
So, I will see that you are nourished
with human blood. (thunder rumbles)
- [Crow] I have a question.
- He is here.
Listen to our cry, oh
inscrutable lord of darkness.
- [Servo] I'm doing it.
- Imponderable King of
with craft and black magic.
Protect us under your great powers.
- [Mike] Dugh, okay.
- Render us invulnerable to the assaults
and attacks of mortals.
- [Crow] Anything else?
- Shield our bodies and our
eyes form the sign of the cross.
And help us to avoid daylight.
- [Servo] And daylight. Yes.
- Our worst enemy is the sun.
- [Servo] Now hold on, let
me write this all down.
- Don't make us touch
fire that purifies all.
- [All Vampire Women]
Let this be your will,
oh lord of darkness.
- [Mike] Yes, oh sorry.
Stepped on stepped on the plug there.
- [Crow] The Devil doesn't like me.
- [Servo] Shark.
(wolf howls)
- [Mike] Some of them
went on to start Hole.
♫ We love (mumbles)
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
- Selene hear my cry.
- [Crow] D I C T O R Y
- Let your immortal rays touch us.
Give me the appearance that I'll need now.
I must have beauty in order
to fulfill my mission.
- [Servo] I think she looks good now.
- You are the breath that
gives life to my body.
- [Mike] Quite kissing up.
- You are my spirit,
and awaken your sleeping slaves as well.
- [Crow] Mexico really
needs a Martha Stewart.
- My servant.
- [Crow] Hey, pretty good first try.
- [Servo] Another successful
José Eber makeover.
- [Crow] I'm pretty so I have value now.
- [Mike] She has to hold her
arms up till her roll-on dries.
- [Crow] They got some pretty
busy spiders in these here
horror movies.
- [Servo] Um-hum.
- [Mike] Ah yes, the
three Russian aviators.
- Selene hear my cry.
- [Servo] (crys like a baby)
and awaken your slave.
- [Crow] Selene.
I believe I asked you
nicely to hear my cry.
- And you.
The dead.
- [All] The dead, woo. The dead.
- Awaken from the sleep
that has kept you silent
for 200 years.
- [Mike] Silent except for
Ted, boy was he sawing logs.
- [Servo] Ah, Tim Allen.
- [Crow] So for 200 years
nobody tried to develop this
castle into upscale town homes?
(ominous music)
- [Mike] Oh, must not
have worn his head gear.
- [Servo] A Jackie Mason.
What am I doing here?
Why am I in a castle?
Why am I in a crypt?
I'm a vampire.
- [Mike] Oh geez, I've
been awake since 1890.
- [Servo] Oh, it has come undone.
We could have left anytime.
- [Crow] I like Lee.
- [Mike] This guys change
is a little more subtle.
- [Servo] They've give
him better arch support.
- [Crow] Oh, Skipper!
- [Mike] It's the Pips.
- [Crow] (sniffs) Do I smell bacon?
- Follow me.
- [Mike] Looks like a Stewart
Anderson's cattle company.
- [Crow] Ugh, just do
what she does I guess.
- [Servo] Boy, I'd be nervous
sleeping under that chandelier.
- [Mike] There's no
railing here, so look out.
- [Servo] Did you ever
see a Polish magnet?
Here, it's over this way.
(snickers)
- [Mike] Which one is Brad Pitt?
(owl hoots)
- [Servo] Oo, ah, well,
I took a wrong turn.
- [Mike] Oh, I know.
She woke them up so that
they could move the couch.
- [Crow] Don't I look fat in that picture?
- Look at her.
200 years ago she was selected
by the King of the dark
dominion to succeed our great Thorena.
It was your fault that she
fled from the hand of my
sister vampires.
- [Mike] We're confused.
- Yes, at that time an extraordinary girl.
Dedicated to a life of virtue
caused us to fail in our
sacred duty.
- [Mike] I'm a crappy vampire.
- Her beauty and kindness were handed down
to a descendant of hers.
And so tonight you will all see her.
When she has reached her
21st year we must capture her
so that she'll be here to
take part in our great ritual.
- [Servo] Now lets get out
there and take it to 'em in the
second half.
- Remember if you fail this time,
- [Mike] It's hard for
women to be managers.
- I have great power
and I will destroy you.
You'll be converted into dust.
Understand?
- We swear we will not
fail you again, Tandra.
- [Crow] That's permafrost to you mister.
- Thorina needs blood and my
sisters and I need it also.
She needs young blood.
- [Mike] Eek.
- That is our job tonight.
- [Mike] That's a mouse.
- Follow me, we'll search for human blood.
- [Crow] I say we start
by searching for humans.
- [Servo] Oh wait, my string is tangled.
Oh, God.
- [Mike] They were going to
have vampires take the form
of squirrels, but it wasn't the same.
- [Crow] So she was
Nora Dunn 200 years ago?
- [Servo] (chuckles) I guess.
(piano music playing)
♫ as time goes on ♫
- [Mike] I dedicate
this song to Thorazine.
- [Crow] (snores) I'm bored.
Bored (snores)
- [Servo] She's auditioning
for Freddy de Cordova.
- [Mike] I don't recall a
second and third movement.
- [Crow] Remember when we had
to listen to her stand up act?
- [Mike] Sure I'm a little tight,
but I think I can get through it.
- [Servo] I'm going to break
into some heavy blues now.
- [Crow] (shuddering breaths)
No, no, no.
You naughty boy.
Don't look at me.
- [Mike] Now Dean Martin
is going to come in
and jump on the piano.
- [All] (laugh)
- [Servo] Hey, the woodland
creatures love her music.
- [Crow] I don't get the
physics of a hovering bat.
- [Mike] The vampire position
flight team, in formation.
- [Mike] I don't' know how
long I can keep this up.
Wait, wait.
There's the note that
I like, yeah. Ugh-huh.
- [Crow] We'll go wait in the car.
Just wanted to fly over with you,
make sure you got here safe.
- [Mike] Her fingering is appalling,
and her phrasing is confused and messy.
- [Servo] (belches and sighs)
- [Crow] I'm really wasted.
- [Servo] The Mexican, Larry Tate.
- [Crow] El Stevens.
- [Servo] Oh, (gurgles).
- [Mike] Loan me your sweater.
- [Servo] I want to loan her my sweater,
and I don't need it back.
- [Crow] Just like Count Basie.
One more time.
- [Mike] Beethoven from the
grave renounces his great work.
- [Servo] Hey great.
You know that thing from Peanuts?
- [Crow] I'm blitzed and
I don't care who knows it.
- [Mike] General Hospital.
- [Servo] She's charging. Look out.
- [Crow] I'm sorry you
couldn't get a better seat,
but we're sold out.
(ominous music)
- [Servo] Scout?
- [Mike] If bats got into his hair,
they'd drown in the Vaseline.
- [Servo] Well, the
bats liked your playing,
they were very supportive.
- Diana what happened to you?
- I don't know, George.
But it all was so strange.
All of a sudden I heard
a voice calling me from
a tremendous distance.
- [Servo] Saying drink more gin.
- There wasn't anything out there.
Could have been a bird.
I think I saw something fly.
- It's most likely that
you're nervous, Diana.
You know I bet is was
a butterfly out there
attracted to the light.
And that's all.
- [Crow] Or a tiny condor
waiting for you to die.
- I guess that you were right.
It was only my nerves.
George dear, you know tomorrow
we announce our wedding
plans during the party--
- [Servo] We do? What the?
- Tomorrow is my birthday.
- Right, and now that you're
feeling better darling,
remember we're going out.
- Ugh, George.
I'd prefer that Diana stay
here in the house tonight.
- Why professor?
- I don't know really, but she's fatigued
and better rest tonight.
- Papa's telling the truth, dear.
I'm a little tired, and I
prefer to go to bed early.
And tomorrow I'll feel much better George.
Is that okay?
- Alright then, you win.
- [Crow] Them.
- Anyway, pretty soon
you'll be using my name,
and I'll give the orders around the house.
- [Servo] You will be my slave.
- Don't you agree, professor?
- Huh? (chuckles)
Oh yes, certainly. Of course.
- Good night George.
- Tomorrow you'll feel better.
- [Mike] Oh, the passion.
- I'm going up, Papa.
- Get a good rest darling.
- [Crow] Wait, when did
you get that tattoo?
You get back here.
Don't you ignore me.
Well, good night.
- Professor,
- [Mike] Your daughter is hot.
- I know something is worrying you.
You're trying to hide it.
- No, no, it's nothing.
The trouble is that you're
a little nervous also.
You're imagining things.
- Well I don't know,
you seem to be acting
pretty strange tonight.
- Yeah, but.
- [Crow] It's so funny
that you would think that,
just because you say I'm acting strange.
I, I don't know.
- Sorry but I don't agree with you--
- [Crow] That guy has a funny voice.
- [All] (laughing)
- You're not going to
be loosing a daughter.
On the contrary, you'll be gaining a son.
(doors slam shut)
- Come on, Mike.
How do you play this game?
- Well, it's pretty easy,
you just move a piece
and you go
♫ stratego ♫
- Oh.
Think I can do that.
Move a piece there.
♫ Stratego ♫
- Oh I get it.
- Hey, hey look you guys.
Look, look, look.
- Sure Crow, anything to win, eh?
- Come on, we're right in
the middle of a game here.
Come on.
♫ Stratego ♫
- But it's right there.
He's right there.
- Sure, whatever.
- I think it's a star child.
What?
Really?
Oh, when?
Oh I see.
Yes.
Yes, of course.
It all makes sens now.
♫ Stratego ♫
- Alright Crow, your turn.
- Something is going to happen, Mike.
Something wonderful.
- I know, I'm about to win.
♫ Stratego ♫
- Hey.
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
- [Servo] Ugh-huh, that's right Crow.
- [Mike] Not sure I understand that game.
- Tell me inspector, you
working on an investigation?
Or stopping a crime?
- I just came to say hello
to my dear old friend
Professor Orlof.
And to say that since Diana
is starting a new life,
we can play chess every night now.
- [Servo] Chess?
- Buy you're coming to the
masquerade ball aren't you?
- Yes, I guess so.
I'll be coming as Sherlock Holmes.
Although I haven't received my invitation
as yet, unfortunately.
- [Crow] That's fast.
- But that's why I asked you come tonight.
I wanted to give you the
invitation in person, inspector.
- [Servo] Let me go write it, quick.
- Well I'll say good night.
See you tomorrow inspector.
- Goodbye for now, George.
- See you tomorrow, Professor.
- Sleep well, George.
- [Crow] Some butlers stay inside, sir.
- [Servo] Shut up and get outside.
- [Crow] Yes, sir.
- Please come into the
private study, Charley.
- [Mike] What was that all about?
- [Crow] Please walk through the door
into the private study, Charley.
- [Mike] He's got a picture of
Ready Kilowatt up over there.
- [Servo] I'm very shy around inspectors.
- Now why all the mystery.
I can see that you're
anxious to speak to me.
- [Servo] I am not anxious,
it is you who are anxious.
- You see, Diana is in terrible danger,
but what's a good way
to enplane it to you?
- [Mike] Puppet theater?
- Well that's easy, start by explaining.
- (sighs) I can't Charles.
I'm at a loss.
- Be Frank, I want to
hear all the details.
I'm to understand that Diana
could be in danger, Professor.
I've been summoned here
because you hope I'll find
an adequate way to protect her.
Isn't that true?
And never-the-less,
you can't or won't tell
me what is happening.
- [Servo] And that makes it
hard to get the scene going.
- How can you expect any help,
when I don't know who it is
I must protect your daughter from?
- Charles,
I'm usually quite direct
and I don't like secrets,
but in this case, I
hesitate now because you see
I'm not sure yet.
That's about what you'll say.
- [Servo] Oh I, ugh?
- Someone is trying to kidnap
Diana, so they can collect
ransom from you, come on now, speak up.
- No, no, I swear it's not true Charles.
No its something far more
terrible than death it's self,
it's horrifying, I'm at a loss.
- [Servo] But forget I said anything.
- That's all I'm going to tell you now.
Should you decide to help me, fine.
If not, then leave me alone.
- [Crow] Look, you invited me here.
- Now take it easy, Professor.
I'll help you, and willingly, but how?
- [Servo] I can't tell you.
Now leave me alone.
- Tomorrow night, I'd like
you to gather together some
men, and good men, and
come to the party, Charles.
I mean to protect Diana.
- [Mike] Now get out of here.
- Now look, if she's in danger
why not suspend the party?
- That's impossible.
Diana's very sentimental, it's
only what the girl deserves.
But at the same time she
can't know the facts either.
My, the situation is desperate now.
- But Professor, let me
know what's happening here,
simply for Diana's good.
- No, don't insist.
I repeat I can't say anymore, Charles.
Now, do me a favor, leave me alone.
I have work to get done tonight.
- [Crow] Be sure to
stop by again tomorrow,
and then leave immediately.
(laughter)
- [Mike] No wait, come back.
- [Crow] Why won't he help me?
- [Mike] Please shut the
film off, and discuss now.
What would you have done to
make this a better party?
- [Servo] If only I had a television set.
- [Crow] Hey, he's a CB owner.
I wonder what his handle is?
- [Mike] Better review the
rules of etiquette again.
- [Servo] I'll consult
my sacred roll of Brawny
- [Crow] Ah, they let Billy
draw up today's pamphlet.
- At the end of 200 years,
- [Mike] I'll tell him something.
- Tandra will seek revenge in
one of Rebecca's descendants.
This unfortunate young girl
will inherit the beauty that
her ancestor enjoyed,
and when she becomes 21 years of age,
she will be initiated into
the black rituals of the
vampire women to succeed Thorina,
- [Servo] Page two.
- On her left shoulder
she will carry the figure
of a vampire, the unmistakable
sign of her tragic destiny.
- [Mike] Her tragic destiny
was announced by her parents
of Red Wing, Minnesota.
- [Servo] I looked better
before I tried to look good.
- [Mike] Owe. Owe. Owe.
- [Crow] Butterfield Ocho.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Now when was I
a flying leather neck?
- [Servo] Bothered by
unsightly demon marks?
- [Crow] I shouldn't have
gotten drunk at Sturgis.
- [Servo] I'm responding to
your let's get acquainted add.
(screams)
- [Mike] I suppose I have to read her
the Very Hungry Caterpillar again.
- [Mike] I'm going to have
this room sound proofed.
- [Crow] Huh, Garth Hutchinson is outside.
- Diana what happened?
- [Mike] But I can't stay
long, so don't tell me.
- (crying)
There was face behind the window.
It was simply hideous, Papa.
Dead and ugly.
- [Servo] Don't talk about
your mother that way.
- And so diabolical, it seemed
to be spying on me through
the window.
- [Crow] Mind if I throw that
butterfly theory at you again?
- Calm down, darling.
Calm down.
You didn't see anything,
you're only nervous.
You're imagining things.
- No, I can't forget that
incident down stairs.
When I was sitting at the piano,
and then this horrible face,
it's not my imagination, dad.
This is all real.
- [Mike] Ugh-huh.
- I know it, I can't find
an explanation for it.
I know that it exists and I'm afraid, dad.
- [Servo] You're getting
Ponds on my suite.
- Come on, sweet heart.
Please calm down.
I repeat, you didn't see anything.
Have faith in your father.
- [Mike] You're probably just crazy.
- It has a meaning.
I was born with this, and you know it.
- [Crow] Your arm?
Yes, it's true.
I always wanted to know what it meant,
and you always refused to tell me, dad.
Now what is it?
Isn't it strange it should
be shaped like a vampire?
- It's only a mark like
any other, darling.
I've seen plenty on other persons,
not the same as yours, I know,
but they had some strange shape,
and they didn't mean a thing.
Why not have faith in your dad, darling?
- [Mike] These other persons
were all cast into hell,
of course but.
- Tell me Diana, just where
did you see this thing?
This ugly and horrible face in the night?
- I saw it in the mirror
when I was combing my hair, dad.
- In the mirror, you see?
Didn't you ever read that
light does curious things when
it bounces off a mirror?
It reproduces figures and shadows.
I've been fooled like
that many times, dear.
Why should I try to kid you?
It's not logical.
Come dear, try and get some sleep now.
Should you need me, I'll be in the study.
And there's no need to worry any longer.
- [Mike] Many times lint gets in your eye,
and take on ghoulish shapes,
it happens to everyone.
(chuckles)
- [Servo] Hum.
Whoa, better get some holy water.
Gonna need a cross, some garlic, maybe,
she's so a demon, I can't believe it.
- [Crow] That mirror
thing was pure genius.
(low humming)
- [Mike] We got to get a better fan.
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
- [Mike] I'll send for
your car, Mr Lugosi.
- Thank you, sir.
- [Crow] We had a really
Hispanic time, thank you.
- [Servo] Ah, the entire
Mexican middle class,
ladies and gentlemen.
- [Mike] (shudders)
- [All] (laughs)
- [Mike] Some of the Devil's
minions are cheap thugs.
- [Crow] Over the lips
and through the gums,
look out stomach, here it comes.
- [Mike] Huh?
(whistle blows)
- [Servo] Hey, I got a
load of vampires here.
- [Mike] They didn't count
on Carlton the door man.
- [Crow] It's a vampire wilding.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Tell your friends,
the vampires are here.
- [Mike] I need more eye liner.
(gasps)
- [Mike] Yes, they're real.
- [Crow] Now that's great puppetry.
(bat squeaks)
- [Mike] Trying to catch flies? (chuckles)
- These two blue marks close
together on the victims neck,
are what have me puzzled, inspector.
- Besides that, we didn't
find one drop of blood
in the corps.
Why you could swear that a
vampire murdered the girl.
- Hey, now that I think about
it, I bet those monsters
were vampires, doc.
And right after she attacked the girl,
she changed into a vampire.
She sucked her blood and
then she began to change.
- Take him along boys, and
put under a weeks detention.
- But listen chief, listen I'm not crazy.
I tell you.
It's true, I tell you, it's true.
Those were vampires I saw.
- [Mike] He said the same thing
about a parking violation yesterday.
- Are there any internal injuries, doctor?
- [Crow] No, I'm fine.
- None inspector.
- And those two blue holes there?
Don't you really know what they are?
- No I don't.
I can tell you one thing, and
there's no mistake about it,
my friend.
- [Mike] I'm Cocoa Chenille.
I attribute these two holes
to some strange animal,
who's species is unknown.
And there's no way that
I can determine it.
- [Crow] Well, I think it was the vampire,
but let's keep that guy locked up.
- [Servo] Hum, he seemed disappointed.
I should have made up an answer.
(sounds of physical struggling)
- [Mike] Ah, the Rain Forest Cafe.
- [Crow] They're going
to wax his bikini area.
(heavy sigh)
- [Mike] The torture of Don DeFore.
- [Servo] Now, what do you know
about the door man industry?
- [Crow] They're worshiping
a giant Toblerone?
- [Mike] It's a Mandrel
sisters, Halloween special.
(ominous music)
- [Servo] Who sat on the mascot?
I thought liturgical dance was dead.
- [Mike] Do we have an agenda, Susan?
- [Servo] Would you just
get out of the coffin.
Geesh.
- [Crow] Dive in girls, the buffet's open.
- [Mike] Oh, you got a little,
let me get,
a little, come here.
- [Servo] I'd like to thank the academy.
- Thorina, Queen of the vampire women.
- [Mike] Here.
- The hour for you to acquire
your original beauty has arrived.
- [Crow] I've learned to
appreciate my off beat looks.
- [Mike] She's got combination skin.
One part is fetid, and one part is rotted.
- [Servo] Ladies and
gentlemen, Ms Putrescence.
(humming)
- [Crow] (kissy smacks)
- [Mike] She looks like
a magic eye picture.
♫ Woke up get out of bed
♫ dragged a comb across my head ♫
- [Crow] I am so sure, Debbie
gets to be Queen when she's
been asleep for five centuries.
I mean like I work the
float and everything.
- [Mike] She thinks she's
hot snot on a silver platter,
but she's just a cold
bugger on a paper plate.
- [Crow] She's just princess
Kay, of the yucky way.
(humming)
- [Servo] Hey, how's the snake hanging?
- [Crow] Go play with your ball.
- [Mike] Who didn't use a coaster?
- [Servo] Ah, she's a
member of the mud club.
- [Crow] I swear I'll just nurse this one.
- [Mike] Ugh, I was going
to ask you something,
but I can't remember now.
- [Servo] Guys, the
presences of his pants,
prove there is a god.
- [Crow] The maKing of the
International Male catalog.
- [Mike] You know it's
hotter than hell in here.
- [Crow] I wonder if this is
considered a sweet assignment
for those guys?
- [Servo] You want a sip?
- [Mike] I ordered a Tom Collins.
- [Crow] Don't gob in it.
- Selene, here my cry.
This is the moment,
this is the moment to carry
out the supreme sacrifice.
We must have blood,
and he is ready to die.
- [Servo] I am?
Wait.
- [Mike] We're out of
blood, is Pepsi okay?
- [Crow] Too much middle
management in this organization.
- [Servo] Can I get a softer slab?
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Oh sir, I implore
you to close your legs.
- [Servo] Tab's got sass.
- [Crow] I just came in for a cleaning.
(hisses)
- [Mike] Oh, bite me.
(laughter)
- [Servo] Demi More,
Michael Douglas, Disclosure.
- [Crow] Once you let yourself
go, it feels kind of good.
(smacks lips)
- [Mike] Body by Jake.
- [Crow] Alright, O-negative on tap. Woo!
- [Servo] Hey, somebody tip
him up so we get all of it.
- [Crow] Put us in coach, come on.
(coyotes howling)
- [Mike] This is what southern
Baptists think Catholic mass
is like.
- [Crow] Ah.
- [Servo] (whistles) Who wants blood?
- [All] I do, I do.
- [Servo] So once you drain
the blood, can we just dump it
in the drive way?
- [Mike] No, you gotta
take it to a garage.
- [Crow] Wonder if there
are vegetarian vampires?
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Now, you can't
donate again for a week.
- [Servo] Can you imagine
the huge apocalyptic grease
fire, if they threw
Rush Limbaugh in there?
- [Crow] Yuck.
- [Mike] Oh he's green,
the fires all smokey.
- [Mike] You got me up for that?
- [Servo] He's going to get you so pretty.
- [Mike] Hey, it's Big Ethel.
(chuckles)
- [Servo] He's going to have
a great big blood wrestler.
- [All] Finish it. Woo, woo!
- [Crow] Ah, it must be a Merlot.
(belches)
- [Mike] I'm just waiting
for that click, Maggie.
- [Servo] Anna Maria Alberghetti.
- [Crow] Satan has given
me prominent cheek bones.
- [Servo] There are some
happy vampires here.
- [Mike] She's the Thelma
Ritter of the group.
- [Servo] Will you look
at this rock Todd gave me?
- Let them drink.
Our sisters are impatient.
- [Crow] You think drinKing will help?
- [Mike] Oh, that's it?
I was expecting another order, I'm sorry.
- [Servo] Here honey,
take an extra big sip.
- [Crow] Hey, Lilly snagged in the cup.
- [Servo] And it doesn't always work.
- [Mike] Sade.
♫ Your love is King ♫
- [Crow] Oh.
This Joe Cocker here in the fore ground?
- [Mike] Come on, I just
need a little beauty, man.
Just a little bit.
Please.
Just make me a little bit pretty, come on.
(gasping)
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
♫ Singing in the bath tub ♫
- Hey, check out the faint glow
emanating from deep 13.
- Wow.
- What is with all the
ethereal stuff today?
- (snoring loudly)
- Frank?
- (mumbles)
Awaken my child.
Frank?
- (coughs and sputters)
Jesus?
- No.
- Torgo.
Yes, that was the name.
And thus may you still call me,
though now, I am Torgo the white.
Join me, Frank of TV,
in a beautiful place.
Where all the lackeys and
toddies and whipping boys
are forever safe and free
from their oppressors.
- Sounds great.
Can Dr Forrester come?
- No, the point is you
wouldn't want him there.
- Hey, they fixed your knees, huh?
- There are no bum knees
in my world, child.
- And how about your voice?
- What about my voice?
Now, arise TV's Frank, and
join me, for they are all here.
Tonto, and Cato, and Robin, and
Don Wilson, and Gabby Hayse.
- And Joe Besser?
- Yes.
All of them.
In short,
yes, we have second bananas.
- Wow.
So Torgo is actually working with
two completely reconstructed knees.
That is dedication.
Amazing.
- Frank is gone.
- Well that's amazing too.
- I think that if Frank were still here,
he would want us to say--
(alarm buzzing)
- We got movie sign.
(doors opening)
- [Crow] Wow, huh?
- [Servo] Wow.
- You've seen the girl
chosen as my successor?
- Yes, majesty.
And likewise, I have seen on her skin
the mark that identifies her.
- [Servo] It's a liver spot.
- The dark vampire.
She is truly lovely my Queen,
her beauty rivals yours.
- [Crow] Yeah, right.
- She will be a deserving successor.
Tomorrow is her birthday, she'll be 21.
And we all know the prophecy
says that she is to stand
in your august presence here.
When the ceremony starts, oh Queen.
- [All] We dropped our contacts.
- In a a very few moons, I
am to terminate my reign.
It is written that I am to
return to the depths of the dark
dominion.
If you fail me again, my
vengeance will know no limits.
- Here us, oh Queen, who rules the nights.
Sovereign of the vampire women.
- [Mike] And a good friend.
I shall not fail this time, I promise you.
(thunder rumbles)
- [Servo] If I could just
interject here. (chuckles)
I couldn't help overhearing.
- [Crow] The how and why
book of vampire women.
- [Mike] Oh, why did I agree to proof read
this Michener novel.
(sighs)
- [Servo] Hey, I found a great thermal.
I'm riding an updraft.
- [Crow] Hi.
- [Servo] So she comes, sucks
on your neck, you live for all
eternity, she's super hot,
what's the problem here?
- [Mike] Someone is
undressing me with their eyes.
- [Crow] Ms Tennessee has
wondered away from the home.
- [Servo] Ah, I see the
spanking service has arrived.
- [Mike] Tom.
- [Servo] Well.
- [Mike] Transfer the
counties funds to derivatives.
- [Servo] Anderson
windows and, well hello.
- [Crow] She's got a beefy
assistant with a flash light
crouched in the bushes.
- [Mike] She just got hard contacts.
- [Servo] I know I look
like Vincent Price.
- In God's name I order you to disappear.
Against him and his power you are nothing.
- [Mike] Oh, used the G word.
No fair.
- [Crow] Geez, I don't have
the acceleration I used to.
Eth, this is second.
- [Servo] Geez, I'm as
mental as my loony daughter.
- [All] (raucous laughter)
- I came as soon as I got
your message, Professor.
What's going on?
- [Servo] I feel sort of silly right now.
Did I over dress?
- I think you'll recall
that for years now I've been
translating these crumbling
old parchments here.
- [Mike] Sure, alright.
- They belong to my ancestors.
And in which they announce
the tragic destiny that awaits
my daughter, Diana.
- [Mike] Right, I remember that.
- No, I haven't forgotten.
Tomorrow is the day, Professor.
Diana is about to become of age.
Have you found anything that will help?
- [All] (snickers)
- An important clue that
could be used to stop those
monsters when they try take her?
- I studied it Samson, but
the things I found out are not
encouraging.
And I fear that there is no hope for her.
- [Crow] Should I get into my costume?
- [Servo] (chuckles)
Er, I forgot my bifocals.
- Here they affirm, that
according to the apocalypse,
we're living at a time when
things are perfect for the
resurrection of monsters here on Earth.
Since men are bent on wreaKing
destruction upon the world
today, they'll heed their
selfish desires and use the
tremendous power that nature has given us.
- [Mike] Ugh, do you
need any wrestling done?
- Nuclear energy.
- But there's something worse
than what I mentioned just now.
- [Servo] Are his nipples painted on?
- I spoke to you about that
strange and extraordinary lad,
who saved Rebecca's life.
The documents say that he
also would have a descendant.
An outstanding young man of
enormous strength, destined to
hide his identity under a
silver color mask, Samson.
That extraordinary young
man, is obviously you.
- [Servo] Oh, obviously.
- But I should tell you something else.
According to the prophecies,
even you might fail trying to
protect Diana.
- [Mike] It's a vague prophecy.
All the evil they can muster
is against you in this thing.
And so you might be killed
attempting to save my daughter.
- Never the less I have to continue.
I have to go on the way my ancestors did,
to eliminate evil of all kind.
And human vampires are
monsters that can never exposes
themselves to direct day light.
Surely they use a hideout
of some kind, as a refuge.
And there, possibly, we could
surprise and destroy them.
- I know.
- [Crow] Still, I said it.
- that these symbols here,
refer to their hide out.
But in spite of all my efforts,
Samson, I've failed trying
to decipher their hidden meaning.
- [Servo] That's too bad.
Well I gotta golf date
with Randy the Macho Man.
- But I'll be ready for
anything, so don't worry.
- [Mike] Ugh, should I
follow you over there, or?
- You're coming to the party
to protect Diana, aren't you?
- No Professor, I have other plans.
- [Crow] I'll bet.
- But I'll be responsible
for Diana's safety.
- [Servo] Hum, another man gone.
Is there something about my
study that drives people away?
Hum.
("Blue Danube Waltz")
- [Mike] Eh, Mexico is one goofy country.
- [All] (laughter)
- [Mike] I don't know, I just
came home and they were here.
- [Servo] Any bad puppets?
Yup, no bad puppets.
- [Mike] Why is he wearing a waste basket?
I came dressed as a Mexican.
- [Servo] They are chaperoning
the hell out of this party.
- [Crow] This party is out of control.
- [Servo] Tonight we're going
to party like it's 1959.
- Now don't forget my instructions.
No one is to enter this
house without an invitation.
- Very well, sir.
- [Mike] Jeeves final
years, is exile to Mexico.
- [Crow] I'd like to apologies in advance
for our wedding night.
- [Servo] Hey, she was
supposed to come as a bat.
- [Mike] Looks like the
guy from house party.
- [Crow] Oh yeah, it's
Kid, or Play. Something.
- [Mike] Geez, and they
call us the undead.
- Are you feeling ill?
- [Servo] I gorged myself on a cracker.
- Just for a moment there, I was dizzy.
Let's sit down, please.
- [Crow] It's a rocken party.
What with the Strauss, and the dancing.
- [Servo] I never thought
I'd long for a mariachi band.
- My poor girl is happy.
- [Servo] (sniffs)
- Just watch her face.
She of course doesn't
suspect that tonight could be
really tragic for her.
- [Crow] You have an odd way about you.
- Don't worry so much about it, Professor.
Why do you think we're here?
We'll stop any attack
that they could begin.
- [Mike] Provided the attack is lame,
and poorly thought out,
and it's our grandma's.
- [Crow] Mickey Spillane,
locked out of another society party.
♫ I have often stalked
down this lane before ♫
- [Mike] So then, I
sailed around Cape Hope,
and of course, King Ferdinand,
he's a really good friend
of mine, you know I could introduce--
- [Crow] You killed one of
the Dutch Masters, you fiends.
- [Servo] Geez, this one is really hard.
(grunting)
- [Mike] Ah, good. My order's up.
- [Crow] Well, that's our limit.
- [Mike] Mmm.
- [Servo] Oh Giorgio, makes me gag.
- [Crow] Nope. Never lost a party guest.
- [Mike] (grunts and sighs)
- Now hide them.
In a little while we'll be back.
- [Crow] She must have
drank Chinese blood.
- [All] (chuckles)
- [Mike] Boy I tell ya,
you only rent blood, huh?
(chuckles)
- [Servo] Meanwhile, back at
the worlds most joyless party.
- [Crow] Please stop playing the waltz.
- [Mike] I only wish he was in costume.
- Now do you feel better?
- Mm-hum.
- [Servo] How about now?
Do you feel better now?
What if I do this?
Is this better?
Better now?
Now? Huh? How about now?
- [Crow] Yo, here's my invite.
- [Mike] Mr and Mrs Vampire,
of Passaic, New Jersey.
- [Servo] They're actually
going to perk up this party.
- [Crow] You are not the Kissinger's.
- Please excuse the question, but--
- [Servo] Would you sleep with me?
- [Mike] Maybelline, fine
makeup sensibly priced.
- [Crow] I will get your cream of wheat.
- [Mike] Good job Ted,
you were firm but fair.
- She okay then?
- [Servo] I'd say she's hot,
hot, hot. (laughs oddly)
- [Mike] Oh good, they're
finally putting the salmon out.
- [Crow] She's totally
attracted to my hat.
- [Servo] Hi, wanna look inside my hat?
- [Mike] Come on over, go ahead
and look at the sweat band.
- [Crow] I did the
glitter myself. (chuckles)
- [Servo] You home wrecker.
- [Mike] You know what they say
about guys with big hats, huh?
- [Servo] (chuckles) You
know, once you go Cossacks,
you never go back. (chuckles)
- [Mike] Aren't some of
the costumes here weird?
Yeah.
- [Crow] Hey, you wanna wrestle?
♫ Ten minutes ago I met you
♫ and we murmured our how do you dos ♫
- [Mike] Okay.
I should tell you that some time ago
a prophecy was spoken of,
Oh what the hell, give
me another black Russian.
- [Crow] I just realized that
is a totally boring party.
Let's bring out the peyote.
♫ Bup, bup, bup ♫
- Capture her.
Hurry inspector.
(whistle blows)
- [All] (barking)
(screaming)
- [Servo] Hey, make out time.
(kissing noises)
- [Mike] This should
have happened hours ago,
the party is finally coming to life.
(laughter)
- Get that man, he's carrying her away.
- [Crow] Oh, Mr Wayne.
- [Servo] Ugh-oh, more
supernatural Tom Foolery.
- [Mike] Wanna buy a watch?
- Don't fire.
Your bullets could wound her.
♫ Duh, duh, duh, ta
♫ Duh, duh, duh, ta ♫
(gun shots)
- [Crow] Or go ahead and
fire, whatever you think.
- [Servo] (chuckles)
- [Mike] Hut, hut.
They've got the Polka Queen.
No.
- [Crow] Wee, it's fun being
the eternal damned, woo.
Come on Skipper.
- [Mike] He's got the ball at the 20.
The 10, he could go all the way.
- [Servo] (imitates air
plane engine going by)
- [Crow] It's the Santo Mobile.
- [Mike] I can't believe I forgot my cup.
- [Servo] Hey, mom said you
guys have to let me play.
Oh, ooh.
(smacks and grunts)
- [Mike] Did we have a
plan for this, people?
- [Crow] The undead recruits of the WWF.
- [Mike] Where are the cocktail whines?
- (grunts) Yah.
- [All] (chuckles)
- [Servo] Hut, hut.
Alley oop.
Oh, hog pile.
(grunts) Pink belly.
- [Crow] Oh, titty twister.
Not fair.
- No, not yet.
Samson is fighting against them now.
Wait till they're separated.
- [Mike] Oh, they separated?
That's too bad.
(mumbles)
- [Servo] Oh, now they
gotta call Joan Embery.
- [Crow] Get the tennis rackets.
- [Mike] (imitates bat wing noises)
- [Servo] The Malabo get away car.
- [Mike] Just leave me out here, I'm fine.
I'll sleep, it's cool out here.
Please.
- [Crow] Do you think you
can still schottische?
(police siren wailing)
- [Servo] All right you folks
need to turn down the Strauss
a little bit.
There's been some complaints.
- We heard shots from this direction.
Is anything wrong, inspector?
- Nothing, nothing.
You can go now.
- [Mike] Thank you, thank you.
I'll go now.
(car engine revs)
- Chief I saw two corpses in the garden.
- [Servo] Oh, bye.
- Just a moment.
- [Servo] (chuckles)
- not a word about the things you saw
here in the garden tonight.
Or they'll put us in the
booby hatch, I'm sure of that.
- [Servo] Blah, bleh.
- That's exactly what we were thinKing.
- Tell the jailers to free
that little officer that
informed us about the flying vampires.
And call for an ambulance, too.
- Right, chief.
Come on, boys.
- [Crow] Even after dispatching
orders, I feel empty.
Well.
- [Mike] And that was when I
was captain of the pep squad.
- I never wold have believed
it, if I hadn't of seen it
with my own eyes.
- Now you know why I hesitated
to explain it to you.
- Don't you have the slightest idea
where to find the hideout that
these creatures are living in?
(phone rings)
- [Servo] Ah, that must be
one of my many wrestling
acquaintances.
- [Crow] (imitates odd ringing
sound) Oops, pardon my phone.
- Hello, this is the
residence of Professor Orlof.
Yes.
For you Charles.
- [Mike] Make it quick,
we got a movie going on.
Okay.
- Thank you.
Yes.
I'm the inspector.
Go ahead.
- [Servo] No, I don't know
the Count of the Amount.
(ominous music)
- Alright.
I'll be there later.
- [Crow] I have to go home
and empty the dish washer.
- Another pair was attack in
the same spot as last night.
They'd been in the night club also.
The poor girl was killed,
and they found the same small
holes in her neck.
Her escort was kidnapped.
- [Mike] They kidnapped her car?
What was the point of that?
- [Crow] Her car?
- Now that's an idea.
- [Servo] Put the cheese
inside the cracker.
- The crimes that were committed
there these last two nights
could furnish us with a clue.
- [Servo] Copernicus?
- It's evident that they use
that area to attract their
victims in some way.
- [Mike] Hello, anybody here?
- I think we'll have to play
all our cards at this time.
It'll be morning pretty soon.
- [Servo] Abner, Abner, look.
- Tomorrow night we'll
go to that night club,
and we'll take Diana with us.
- Are you out of your mind, Charles?
- [Crow] You're a mean one Mr--
- Under the circumstances,
Diana is in just as much danger
here as she would be in any other area.
Now don't worry.
I'll send guards to surround the block,
and they won't cause suspension.
My best trained men are going
to be in that night club too.
- Now look what happened out
there in the garden tonight?
And your men's bullets
couldn't detain those infernal
creatures, Charles.
- Yes, but all in all, I don't
think anything is going to
happen to Diana.
And on the other hand it's
quite possible that we'll find
out who those monsters are
and that diabolic female
that leads them.
It's a chance, but they
could reveal their hide out.
So now please have
confidence in me, Professor.
If you don't you'll be
running a great risk,
and you might not save Diana.
- [Servo] And the risk is?
- Is right, Papa.
Sooner or later those
monsters are going to find me,
why not try it as a last resort.
Anything is preferable to
continuing this nightmare.
- The plan just might work too, Professor.
- You win.
I'll go along with you.
- No, Professor.
You should stay here,
and wait to hear from Samson.
Now try to get a little rest Diana.
The house is under constant guard.
- [Mike] Now lets get back
to the party and Strauss out.
- [Servo] Let's get you back
to the Lawrence Welk show.
- [Mike] I thought we
drained 'em pretty good,
how about you?
- [Servo] Yeah, we're
getting pretty good at this.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] Let's see, one,
two, watch your kidneys.
(grunts) up we go.
Heavy sucker, huh?
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Servo] So, you guys going over
to Steve's after the shift?
- [Mike] Okay Shelly.
Truth, dare, double
dare, promise or repeat.
- You have failed me once again, Tandra.
- [Crow] You kyped my eyeliner.
- There is a terrible
enemy in our away, Thorina.
His name is Samson, and he is to blame.
The girl that was chosen
as your successor,
was in our power when
he got there tonight.
But tomorrow he'll be dead, Thorina.
This I swear in the name of your husband.
The King of the Dark--
- [Mike] I am watching the game.
- You know I must terminate my reign soon.
So tomorrow you are to
have my successor here.
My vengeance is cruel and terrible.
- [Mike] Phyllis Newman has gone nuts.
- As well as your sisters will be changed,
to dust.
(thunder roars)
- [Crow] That's what happens
if you don't moisturize.
- [Servo] Great, there
goes half the bowling team.
- [Crow] Key-ripes.
- [Mike] Fiends are visiting from Europe.
- Give me another opportunity,
I shall not fail again.
- Tundra I wish to see
my successor tonight.
Take me to her.
- You order and I obey, sovereign.
- [Crow] You're damn straight.
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
(singing in Spanish)
- You're wanted on the telephone, sir.
- [Crow] It's Lucy Ricardo,
she wants to be in the show.
- [Servo] Hey this isn't Strauss.
- [Mike] Thank you, thank you.
That was (speaKing gibberish)
- [Servo] Two for the ViKings.
I've got two for the ViKings.
- [Crow] That Danny Deviot has arrived.
- Why do you suppose
they want the inspector?
- Oh, I...
- [Mike] Ah-ha, indeed.
Well put.
♫ We will cross the
Imperial as running dogs ♫
- [Crow] There's always
a line in the ladies ro--
oh.
- I was speaKing to Professor Orlof.
Samson hasn't phoned, and he's worried.
I understand that tonight
he fights at the arena.
So maybe he'll get in touch
with us a little later on.
- [Mike] This must be the arena.
Where Samson is fighting tonight.
Perhaps he'll get in
touch with them later on.
- [Servo] (chuckles)
Oh, they're making the
beast with two butts.
- [Crow] You know it actually looks fun.
- [Mike] Says you.
They were the inspiration for
the Pilobolus dance company.
- [Crow] The ruling party
set the debate format.
- [Servo] (humming)
- [All] No!
- [Crow] Sure they made
fun of him in High School,
but just look at him now.
- Before I have my match with Samson.
Gonna be a real tough fight.
- [Servo] Oh, butt crack.
Look out.
Oh. (coughs)
- Make sure you lock the door, Willie.
I don't want nobody to disturb me.
- [Crow] (chuckles) He looks
like an executioner on break.
- [Mike] Mount man.
Wow.
- [Servo] Hey, you're out
of toilet paper in here.
- [Crow] I was sent by fantasy gram.
♫ Loves a wrestler ♫
- [Servo] Oh, someone let me down there.
- [Crow] Mr Wrestler, are
you trying to seduce me?
- [Mike] This scene was
cut out of Spartacus.
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Oh, it's a Robert
Mapplethorpe coital session.
(screams and grunts)
- [Crow] (imitates choking sounds)
You have a kind face.
- [Mike] Come to the dark side,
or I'll take your lunch money.
- [Servo] (imitates strangling sounds)
- [Mike] I'll see you in hell.
Oh, actually I will.
I'm down there a lot, so.
- [Crow] Ah, crap.
It's the wrong guy.
- [Servo] Yup, now I better dress him,
and tie him to the fender,
and get him home.
- [Mike] Then there's all
the paper work down in hell.
(crowd cheering)
- [Crow] Oh, woop, ooh.
Oh gee, should have seen that one coming.
- [Servo] This is one of the weirder
parts of the Menendez trial.
- [Mike] I can see why Cindy
Lauper loves this sport so.
- [Crow] It's Andy El Kaufman.
- [Servo] Why can't they
just talk about whatever is
bothering them instead of
this senseless wrestling?
- [Crow] Owe, Ooh.
That hurt me.
(sniffing)
- You're on now.
- [Mike] Say, is your body
remarkably different from
when I was just in here.
- [Servo] It's a little
chilly in the ring tonight,
take this light wrap, okay honey?
- [Mike] Let's go to our
night in the theater.
- [Crow] Ding, ding.
We need a volunteer.
- [Mike] Sit down.
Everybody sit down.
We're not going to start the match
until everybody sits down.
- [Crow] The wrestling program in hell
is second only to Iowa.
- [Servo] I don't know the
second Schmeling, Satan
fight went on for 15 rounds.
- [Audience] Samson, Samson, Samson.
- [Mike] Thank you.
Thank you very much, but
I'm just the referee.
Thank you.
- Three falls are allowed,
and there is no time limit tonight.
- [Servo] (imitates gravelly vocal tones)
- The main event of the evening.
In this corner here,
the black mask, the challenger.
(crowd boos)
- [Servo] Nobody likes me.
- And here in this corner.
The man in the sliver mask is, Samson.
The champion.
(crowd cheers)
- [Crow] This is what would
happen if Don King took
over opera.
- [Mike] Hey, I didn't ask to see that.
- [Servo] (chuckles)
Okay.
I'll take your coat and
put it in the guest room.
(whistle blows)
- [Servo] Whoop.
- [Crow] Ah yes, the sport John Irving
wrote about so eloquently.
- [Mike] You know before
he became a fallen angle,
Satan was a jock.
- [Crow] This is very
much like the Quite Man,
except Mexicans, and tights,
and one of them is the Devil.
- [Servo] Owe, gee.
You're getting really serious about this.
I mean come on.
Owe.
(doors slam shut)
- Ugh-oh.
That's got to be Forrester.
- Oh, Mike.
I can't find Frank anywhere.
He never stays out this late.
What with his fear of halogen.
I've checked everywhere.
The DQ.
The sewage treatment plant.
All his usual hang outs.
Nothing.
I'm just terribly afraid
that he's gone and he's never
coming back.
And if I cared one iota,
it would be devastating.
If I cared.
- Boy, the boss is
always the last to know.
Well you sir, our time here on
Earth is but a passing thing.
- He was assumed by the Angle Torgo.
In a glorious coronation.
- Well it was kind of a cosmic Torgo.
You see his mission as
a second banana was,
you were kind of mean,
so they ugh.
- Well there was a fortune
cookie which foretold something
about something, and then,
well Gabby Haze is heavily involved.
- Anyway, he's not coming back.
- Sorry.
- Wait.
I can't imagine.
I shan't.
Because it isn't' true.
But it is.
Oh, this sucks.
Who will be my guinea
pig for my gene spicing?
My fingernail transplants?
My fajita?
Who will I blame my mistakes on?
Who will I,
who will I kill?
♫ I've destroyed
♫ I've maimed
♫ And I've kicked him
♫ Now I'm a bully with no victim
♫ No adrenaline thrill
♫ No screams that are shrill
♫ Who
♫ who will I kill?
♫ I've crushed his head a few times
♫ Memories like nursery rhymes
♫ No one died like my TV's Frank
♫ No sweet blood to distill
♫ No cute tummy to drill
♫ Who
♫ Who will I kill
♫ When I look upon the first evening star
♫ I remember when I hooked his
liver to the engine of my car
♫ I could pickle my Aunt Lill
♫ Give my dog a cyanide pill
♫ But what Frank shaped void
would they possibly fill
♫ Here's my money
♫ You can bank it I'm no
good with out my Frank
♫ It's seems he could die
without batting an eye
♫ Now it seems I must
take my own bitter pill
♫ Tell me who
♫ Who
♫ Who will I kill?
(sobs)
Good bye Frank.
And remember, wherever
you are I will kill you.
(sobs and cries)
- Well.
In a sick way I feel touched.
- Yeah.
- We'll be right back.
(sighs)
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
- What's the matter with him?
I swear--
- [Mike] He's got a real
nice way with a song.
- [Servo] Mm-hum.
- [Crow] Don't need to see that again.
- He's been using karate on me.
And he could kill me with one blow.
- Listen, I'll ask that they
suspend the match, Samson.
- No.
I'm going to see this
thing through to the end.
- But you're crazy, he's
trying to murder you.
- I've already been warned about this.
But we'll see.
- [Crow] Can I loose the mask, it's hot.
- [Mike] Oh good.
Give me more wrestling.
- [Servo] Bet the whole place
smells like brie by now.
- [Crow] So much for my fresh new start.
- [Mike] Oh, and the
Devil is out of the ring.
The Prince of Darkness has fallen
on a woman in the front row.
- [Servo] It wasn't such a
good idea to send a killer
vampire into the crowd.
- [Crow] Oh, there you are.
This mask makes it so hard to
know who you should wrestle.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] This isn't
strictly wrestling, is it?
- [Crow] Hum, no.
- [Servo] Um. Ouch.
- [Crow] Let's see, is this melon fresh?
(chuckles)
- [Mike] And the crowd goes wild.
- [All] Yay.
- [Servo] Whop.
- [Mike] Still the audience
could have been seeing jai alai,
or cock fighting.
- [Servo] Ah, Belies.
You'd almost think that
was all planned out.
- [Crow] Samson trained by
watching Road Runner cartoons.
- [Mike] (grunts)
Here that wasn't working, let me try that.
There we go.
- [Servo] Ah, they resort
to second grad tactics.
- [Crow] (laughs)
The international fight
like a girl championships.
- [All] (laugh)
- [Mike] I've engaged in
a bit of pugilism my self.
- [Servo] Your facial peel is
ready to come off now, sir.
- [Crow] Hey come on man,
don't ruin my gimmick.
- [Mike] Don't.
Touch.
Mask.
(chuckles)
- [Crow] Eh, there's a zipper in back.
- [Servo] That's going to be Peter Lopez.
- [Mike] It's part of the
face, it doesn't come off.
- [Crow] It's an Oak Ridge Boy.
- [Mike] (chuckles)
What, what?
It's my butt crack, isn't it?
(crowd screams)
- [Mike] Pan, Texas Ranger.
- [Servo] (chuckles)
- [Crow] Call the pound.
- [Servo] Stay, owe.
You stay in that little--
- [Crow] (high pitched laughter)
- [Mike] Mothra is attacKing the city.
Run, it's Butch Patrick.
(gun shots)
- [Crow] Oh, now you're
just provoking him.
This is Howard Cosell,
how can this be considered
a legitimate sport?
(bats squeaking)
- [Mike] Okay, no more
shapeshifters in the ring.
- [Servo] Terrific floor show, eh?
- Look it's very late inspector,
and I'm starting to get tired.
So what's the use of waiting?
- Just a while longer.
Until daylight.
It's safer, believe me.
- [Servo] We'll get our menus eventually.
- [Crow] Ladies and gentlemen, the Judds.
♫ Sisters, sister
♫ Never were there such devoted sisters ♫
- [Crow] Which twin has the Tony?
- [All] Our wives don't understand us.
- [Mike] Hello ladies,
your special today is a cheesy taco moco.
I'll be back to take your order later.
She's looking at me.
- [Servo] She's looking at me.
- [Mike] Okay then let's get
a Bloody Mary, two straws,
blood sausage, and some blood included.
- There is the girl
chosen as your successor.
Look at her.
She looks exactly like her ancestor.
- She'll be worthy of my thrown.
- [Mike] But I hate her outfit.
- [Crow] Oh God, those bitchy
vampires, Debbie and Jennifer
are here.
- [Mike] She's been stuccoed.
- [Crow] My skin cleared up.
- [Servo] Lillian Hellman on a bad day.
- Ugh, inspector?
Watch the reflections.
Those two in the rear there.
- [Crow] Their checking me out.
- [Servo] Ah, he knows we're ugly.
(mesmerizing music)
- [Mike] Wooo.
(gasps)
(chuckles)
- [Mike] I got a dine
and dash on table four.
(whistle blows)
- [Crow] No running by the pool.
- Arrest those two women.
- [Crow] Any two women.
(whistle blows)
- [Mike] This couple needs a cab.
(engine starts)
- [Mike] The food here is terrible.
And the portions are small.
(breaks squeal)
- Did you see two women come out?
- [Servo] Ugh, no.
- They must be around here.
- [Servo] But I don't--
- Seal off the whole area.
- [Servo] I don't want too.
- Understand?
- [Servo] But we just cam for dinner.
- You two stay here with us.
- [Servo] But we don't--
- We have to give this
young lady protection.
Keep your eyes open.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Where Devil's
go, trouble follows.
- It's time I went back to
wait at the crypt, Tundra.
If you fail again, you know
what there is in store for you.
- [Mike] You have to give me a pedicure.
(bat squeaks)
- [Servo] Eh, we're pretty safe here, eh?
- [Crow] Yup, no danger here.
- [Mike] No danger from vampires--
Whoa!
- [Crow] It's a cool fang funny car.
- [Servo] Oh, neat.
- I think it would be better
if you went back to the house
with Diana.
I'll be waiting here.
My men will go along with you.
- [Servo] (chuckles)
- (screams)
- [Mike] It's the vampire
version of Good Fellows.
- [Servo] Oh real mature vampires,
you big bullies.
- [Crow] Um, I don't need a ride.
Thank you.
- [Mike] You just tell 'em Tony
the big, bad, vampire wants
his money.
- [Servo] Hey, I had this cab.
- [Crow] Hey look, I don't go to Hades,
and if I do it's only during the day.
- [Servo] These vampires
specialize in rough housing
and the black arts.
- [Mike] The Key Stone Vampires.
- [Crow] (chuckles) Boing.
(breaks squeal)
- [Crow] Come here you
mortal son of a bitch.
- [Servo] Turns out it's not Samson,
it's just a very flamboyant CPA.
- [Mike] Woo, ha ha ha.
- [Crow] Whoops.
- [Mike] Circus of the network vampires.
- [Servo] alley oop.
- [Crow] Ah, geez.
I thought I was done for the evening.
- [Servo] (grunts) Getting
too old for these raves.
- [Mike] (sighs)
Oh, give me back my inhaler. (sobs)
- [Crow] The flying Nosferatu brothers.
- [Servo] Samson, party of one.
Your table is ready.
- [Crow] The ultimate battle
between good and evil,
is really goofy.
- [Servo] Up, alley oop, whao, owe.
- [Mike] I didn't fork over
the money for the bat chasing
option on this car, and now I need it.
(car revs away)
(squeal around corner)
- [Crow] Apparently
considerable taxing is necessary
for vampires to lift off.
- [Servo] Okay, up, up and, oh geez.
- [Mike] Death Race Liberace.
- [Crow] Oh, Lady of Fatima
is back and she's pissed.
- [Servo] Oh why couldn't I
have been a vampire in Israel?
- [Mike] It's a sign that
says Wall Drug, 10,000 miles.
- [Crow] Edges light quickly.
- [Servo] Oh, please.
I'll just mark it in my book as a kill.
- [Crow] Can I get you
a glass of water or--
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
- There's no time to loose, Professor.
- [Mike] Eh.
- I'm trying to save Diana,
and it depends on this code.
- [Servo] Just as soon
as I finish this jumble.
- [Mike] There, I really
read him the riot act.
- [Servo] I like you, do you like me?
- A.
B.
- [Crow] C.
D.
- And here,
I think,
- [Mike] Therefore I am.
- At last I've got it.
Thank God.
- [Crow] I've discovered the letter D.
- [Servo] Here, let me
start the gelato machine.
- [Crow] Ah, good.
(machine whirls on)
- [Mike] Ah, sir we should
probably get to rescuing your
daughter?
- [Crow] John Forsythe in bachelor father.
- [All] (laughter)
- Professor Orlof here,
I'm calling you Samson.
This is Professor Orlof, come in.
Can you hear?
It's very important, Samson.
Emergency, please answer.
- I'm listening, Professor Orlof.
This is Samson answering.
Come in Professor.
Over.
- Listen Samson, the crypt
where you'll find the vampires
hiding is located in the
forest of White Pines.
- [Crow] Hugh-huh.
So please hurry.
- [Crow] Good.
I think we may save Diana.
- [Crow] Yeah.
In a second we'll be on our way there.
- [Crow] Okay.
And I wish you good luck.
- [Servo] Yeah, good, whatever.
Look, I got a fair right now.
(machine powers down)
- [Mike] Meanwhile, in
Little Shoe, Wisconsin.
- [Servo] (imitates engine sputtering)
- [Crow] Sometimes when the moon is full,
Samson likes to turn off the
headlights and just drive.
- [Servo] Maybe if Cortes had
never of conquered Montezuma
we would not have had to watch this movie.
- [Mike] Yeah.
♫ Go El Santo
♫ Go ♫
- [Servo] They moved
the action to the Arden.
♫ See the Mexico
♫ In your Chevrolet ♫
- [Crow] Ah, thank
goodness, a wrestle stop.
- [Mike] If a wrestler
falls in the forest,
and there no one to hear it,
does it count as a fall?
- [Crow] (laughter)
- [Servo] Oh, somebody
forgot how to drive.
- [Mike] How come I haven't
noticed that before?
(screaming)
- [Crow] Ah, come on.
Everybody's doing it.
- [Servo] Geez, we haven't
even put the needle in yet.
- No, no. (screams)
- [Mike] Peter Garrett
stars in a very special ER.
- Please leave me alone.
- [Crow] Do we honestly need
another remake of Little Women?
- Tundra in a few short
minutes we will see the dawn.
You must hurry now.
- [Servo] Ah, another hud home for sale.
- [Mike] Wow, man.
This place is like my first
apartment before I got my big
wrestling contract.
- [Crow] I like what they've
done with the cob webs
and bat guano.
- [Servo] (humming pleasant tune)
Cripes what good is being
the ruler of the underworld
if you got to live in a dump like this?
(owl hoots)
♫ Who are you, who, who ♫
- [Mike] Reb-a-ca?
What the hell is Reb-a-ca?
- [Crow] It's a costume, okay?
- [Servo] Your very own
glow in the dark, Samson.
- [Mike] Come on, do something.
Wrestle even.
Well, I mean.
(screaming in distance)
- [Servo] Tell me I didn't hear that?
- [Crow] Hey buddy.
Take it from a wise old
me, don't go in there.
- [Mike] The only problem
with a mask is that it's
really cutting off the circulation by now.
- [Servo] (laughs) Nothing.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Oh, it's a cage match.
- [Mike] Please do not feed the Samson.
(laughter)
- [Servo] Dear God, I
never wanted to see this.
(shudders)
- [Crow] Hey wrestling. (chuckles)
- [Servo] He's got a full acre of area.
- [Mike] Vampires have a pretty
basic agenda with everyone
they capture.
- Tell your sister Tundra, that it's late.
She must hurry.
- [Servo] Tundra, mom says you're late.
- [Mike] Touch downs.
- [Crow] I forgot to put
up the storm windows.
- At last we're going to know
who our stubborn enemy is.
Take off his mask.
- [Servo] Oh I hope it isn't Allen Ludden.
- [Mike] You frighten me. (chuckles)
Wow they must be ugly.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Had they just bought
curtains, it could have saved
the whole vampire race.
- [Servo] Some people
burn easily in the sun.
- [Mike] Hey, you wanna untie
me quick before you die.
So how's your slab, huh?
(chains rattle to the ground)
Oh, yeah, rescue and go.
- [Crow] Okay, but this
is the last time you guys.
- [Servo] No one can
resist a good mix it up.
Alley oop.
- [Mike] Can I get a bendy straw?
- [Crow] Ugh, what was I doing before?
Oh yeah, oh, oh, yeah.
- [Servo] Okay, bye then.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Well see, it's because
they didn't reapply their
sunscreen after sweating.
- [Servo] (humming)
Movie Town News presents,
The March of Time.
Oh damn, Martha Graham dancers.
(screams)
(laughter)
- [Mike] Oh damn, all
the biffies are full.
- [Crow] Panty raid. (laughter)
I'm kidding, of course.
I'm going to burn you to death.
- [Servo] Gee, I hope this
is the right thing to do.
- [Mike] Well, I'll just
let God sort them out.
- [Servo] That's always nice Samson.
Just torch everyone.
- [Mike] Bested at every turn,
and now you've got a chance to
light some helpless women on fire.
(screaming)
- [Crow] Well, I think
that's about everyone.
I'm outta here.
- [Mike] Authorities suspect arson.
- [Servo] Hi honey.
Gee it's great to be back at the castle.
Hope your sisters dress up,
Halloween, slumber party,
went well--
Oh my God!
- [Mike] It's a clown car.
- [Crow] Um, you can put me down.
I can walk.
You don't have to.
I can.
Put.
Could you put.
- [Servo] There's a lot of bodies, Samson.
We got some questions to ask you.
- [Mike] I decided not to burn this one.
- [Crow] Honey I hate to tell you this,
but an android from the
future is going to come
and kill you so you won't give birth.
- [Servo] A thundering tire,
a flashing turn signal,
and a hearty Hi-Ho Silver!
- [Mike] Goodbye sweet wrestling friend.
- God bless Samson.
- Who is he Papa?
- [Servo] God?
Well he's a Judeo-Christian.
- I don't think you'll ever know.
But I'll say this my dear,
- [Mike] He's a fruit cake.
- In this age where there
are certain evil men
who propose to destroy us,
Samson is an example to men of good will,
who serve justice.
- [Crow] Well I do what I can.
I gotta go rinse out a few things.
- [Mike] What a dope.
(doors slamming)
- Well guys, Frank is gone
and maybe now would be a good
time to read our letters to him.
Okay Tom Servo?
- Okay, lets see.
Dear Frank,
Well I guess I better be going.
Yours truly, Servo.
- Kinda short.
- That's nice.
Ugh, Crow how about you?
Do you have a nice letter?
- Dear Frank, you are a pig.
Love Crow.
- [All] (laughter)
- Come on you guys.
Now you're making fun of a guy
who's been very nice to us.
- Yeah.
- I mean sure Frank's dumb,
but you know we could
have had it a lot worse.
I bet Gypsy's letter is more appropriate.
- Yeah, thanks Mike.
Dear Frank, I'm glad that
you are in a better place.
Forrester is evil
and you have been a
welcome touch of kindness.
Others may put you down,
but I will always say,
give me my TV's Frank,
and when he shall die,
Cut him into tiny stars,
and he shall make the
face of heaven so fine,
that all the world will
fall in love with the night,
and pay no heed to the garish sun.
Amen.
- That was beautiful.
Not as poetic as Dear
Frank, you are a pig,
but still.
What?
♫ Maybe Frank,
♫ About Frank
♫ Cause Frank is ♫
Frank?
It really is you?
Speak to me Frank,
speak to me.
- Clay, close your robe.
- Oh, sorry.
- Oh, I just thought I'd check in
from the ethereal outer world,
and see how you're doing.
- Frank I can't believe I
won't be able to kill you
anymore.
- Don't worry, Clay.
Because somewhere deep inside your soul,
you'll always be killing me.
(chuckles)
And remember this, my sentimental friend.
Even though I will
forever be in your heart,
till the end of your days you'll
be a profoundly lonely man.
- Thank you, Frank.
That's very kind of you.
- And just let me say this to
anyone out there who's working
for an abusive boss.
Do not despair.
Never let him crush your spirit,
even if he's already crushed your skull.
Always be your self,
and wave your freak flag high.
- Geez it must be horrible
to work for boss like that.
Frank?
- Hum?
- Could I ask you one thing before you go?
- Sure.
- Could you,
push the button Frank?
- (chuckles)
Watch me rock.
(weird swallowing sound)
("MST3K Love Theme" by Mike Nelson)
(siren wailing)
- Chief I saw two corpses in the garden.